We are now going to move into our regular meeting of the Miami City Council for today's date.
Item number two is public input, unscheduled personal affairs and this was anyone in y'all that said what should Jim address
The council on any at VHM died? They're being maddened out three as a consent agenda staff who has recommended items four through nine
For their consent agenda if there aren't no questions we have emotions
I was going to talk about coach Grover but i think he took a phone call.
Commending is that one of the items,
Correct? Yes any other term it
Any at all in this
January 21st or 23rd stop time again
So we are requesting use as a suffocator for those dates
That's Thursday Friday and Saturday
You have number teams
We have 48 teams this year
That usually generates about 7800 students can come on the NEO campus in a city of Miami
And then number fans to coming into area
I don't know that thousand obviously
Any at all term is one
The biggest event for those cities host or any Lhost
Any given years
You need other questions you're going out with your permit
All right, thankyou coach
Our role entertain emotion
For the consent agenda about it is 467 and 9
I'll second vocal
Chose
Western
And then i also make a motion to approve item eight as a separate items
Second one
Chosen
Question
Hi
Okay, we are now on item 10
Business Dean, the business
Not any of this in stroner
I don't want to let them start for ports
So you're packet and staff available if your questions
And 12 per unit council announcements
A guy one mayor
As most of us know our mime
On 25th is March 3rd 2 5th
And there's talk, preliminary talks right now
We're having a good rich employee
Reunion February 27th
That is the tentative date
Be here at this evening to back with all
Right Now thank you doc and museum
I'll have their example
We will be more on that later, we may have the time
We don't end by then so
So it was half of week before
That's the week before
The 27th is on Saturday
All right, you got to be a former good rich employee
Or related anyway
To one of us
It will have their exhibits there
Thanks for having me.
I'm 13 in city manager communication team
You're going
We are talking about
Council member Johnson has mentioned this
We've also had some calls to the CBB about
The mime on 125
In a lot of people might have noticed
Flyer for commemorative gun
For them 120 fifth anniversary
Very handsome
Fire arm
It's basically in Great and Gold
That has, I believe
A lot
Of what we're wondering is that an official part
With 150th anniversary
No it isn't
We're wondering to make it clear that
Basically somebody is taking the initiative
To offer
It's certainly a way of endorsing
The we are also in no ways saying there
There was something wrong with
In other words, you might be really neat
Commembrant if fire arm for someone
But many people were thinking
That they would put out there and
So this society
In the initiative, this is America
It's a way for somebody to
Maybe make some money but also by providing a service
Providing it good that someone would like
We're going
To be putting something on our face with page
Because lot of people are asking
Are you doing those or
Asking about begun and we have nothing
Do do if what so we'll be.
They will probably
We're not going to discourage that
But I think some people will just be wondering
What's official and what is it?
Second item
Thought we'd ask Chuck
To do a quick update on the animal shelter
Councilman Johnson at
The meeting
That where we are at
If you give me better presentation
As you know, we had a meeting
Following the city council
We got few comments from staff
I'm going to say
Few tweaks on plans
With Anderson Engineering last week
Received Monday yesterday
Receive some revised
Plans that have been more
To do.
The next couple days here
Our process then goes to
Purchasing our legal department
To before it
Goes out the bid so I'm expecting
By day into that week we'll have
Packed in two
Purchasine and Legal hands for their review
And
Then
We're going
Bring up the speed
Yes,
We're going to have a few minutes
Based on the budget we
We've also
Our intent is spend all of money
Without moving over
A couple items
We put alternate in there that
Things
Maybe additional phases
But if you come under
We're going to go there
So we are trying
To battle that because
We never know what the bids will come in
Till it comes
But with these alternate
We want a way
Sure anybody
That is probably
We have done this project
They don't think
The amount of money
We have to go there
And we'll see
The third one
I want a
I think this is really
A neat project
Central Avenue Bridge
Joe approached me few weeks ago
Just couple of week's
Go actually
And I've basically been in touch with the
Chief at the auto-attron
And I've been working on a
Trip provided $1 million for that bridge
Probably would not be as nice
As it is, if
If we're in the process of putting together
A plaque
For The Bridge
That when identified
Cooperative nature between
The Bridge and the train
It's what they would like to have on
And that will be something included
At a later time I'd like
To bring you a resolution
That we name
A bridge after
When it came in
When when you really look at
That bridge, but
We've done an idea of where
Really nice book is
I think this is good
To go for taking the initiative
On that one because
It's just One of those things
That really recognizes we're all pulling together
Thank you Joe
Thanks Joe
And I'm 14
Executive session
For Shunt to 25OS 307 B1
Do We have a motion
To go into Executive session for the reasons
Outline and agenda item 14
Make a motion
And second
Roll call
Hi
Let's see
The first
How to be executive session
At
At 15
Is municipal attorney David Anderson contract
Dave if you would please make the revisions to
The proposed contract that we discussed
To submit
That do
I'm 16
David Chapman claimed
Dean, i guess
You and Mark are in
What's it, you might need for a day
Out in 17 is adjourned
Do We have a motion
Second
What?
We got some
Shult